themerapp.com 2016-03-06

# Themer by MyColorScreen - Privacy

## PRIVACY POLICY

We are SS Digital Media, LLC, a Pennsylvania Limited Liability Company. To do this, we (and some of our advertising partners) ask for data about you and also create data about your use of Themer. This policy tells you what we do with that data. If you want to jump to a particular section of the policy – click on one of the links below: 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via email at apps@mycolorscreen.com .

  1. #### What data do we collect and how?

We will sometimes ask you for personal data (such as your name, telephone number and date of birth) when you create a Themer registration or when you click to participate in certain activities. We also automatically receive and track certain data about your mobile device (such as your device-type and language preference) and we may create a unique device ID for you so we can recognize you. In some cases we can automatically detect your location data. If you connect with Facebook, Google, or another social network via the Themer app, we may also receive some data from that network (e.g. your Facebook ID, name, profile picture, gender, age, locale and email address).
  2. #### How do we use your personal data?

We may use your personal data for the following purposes:   

    1. to provide you with service offers and the display of customized content, and targeted advertising both on our apps/websites and on other apps/websites that we advertise through,
    2. to communicate with the Themer products and services and customer service issues,
    3. to determine when you link from our app to one of our partner apps, so that we can monitor the level of traffic that we generate for our partner apps,
    4. to ensure the technical functioning of our products and services,
    5. to protect Themer’s copyright,
    6. to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use,
    7. to comply with laws, requests from a government bodies or courts, or to respond to litigation, and
    8. to enable us to use a third party to perform surveys measuring your experiences and use of our services.
  
We may also encrypt and/or aggregate your data with other users' data in order to create statistics about the general use of the Themer apps and websites, which helps us to develop new products and services. We may also share this aggregated data with our business partners and third party advertisers.
  3. #### Sharing data with third parties – key facts and how to opt-out

Third parties (such as companies who advertise through our apps) may require you to provide your personal data in order to access their products, adverts and offers. If you visit or register for a third party product, advert or offer, we may pass some data about your device to that third party (e.g. your tag history and country of registration) so that they can send you offers. However, we won't pass your email address or other contact details to these sorts of third parties without your permission.

Any third parties’ use of your personal data is governed by their own privacy policy (which should be accessible from their website or application). If you do not want third parties to be able to access or use your personal data, you should not register for, click on or use the applicable third party application or product.

##### Sharing with social networks

If you connect your Themer account to Facebook or Google+ certain personal data will be shared with other users of these social networks. 
  4. #### Links to other websites

We may display links to third party websites. Please note that we cannot control and cannot be held responsible for the activities of such websites. You should always read the privacy policy of a website to find out more about how personal data is collected and processed.
  5. #### Use of Cookies

Like most web sites and mobile applications, we use cookies to track site usage, to send you advertisements and to customize your experience of Themer. A cookie is a tiny text or graphics file that resides on your computer, mobile phone, or other device, and allows us and/or our business partners to recognize you as a user. For more detail on how businesses use cookies on websites, please see www.allaboutcookies.org. You can find an overview of the various types of cookies used by Themer and/or our business partners, in the table below.   
Cookie type | Purpose  
---|---  
Essential Operational | These cookies are necessary to allow us to operate the Themer websites and apps as you have requested. These cookies, for example, let us recognize what type of subscriber you are and then provide you with the services to which you are entitled.  
Performance | These cookies are used by us or our business partners to analyze how the Themer websites and apps are used and how they are performing. These cookies do not let us identify users (as all user data is aggregated). They are also used to monitor when you link from our app to one of our partner apps so that we can check what levels of traffic we are generating for our partner apps.  
Functional | These cookies let us operate certain functions of the Themer websites and apps in line with the choices you make. These cookies mean that we can "remember" you in-between visits – e.g. we will recognize your user name and remind you how you customized our services.  
Targeting/advertising | These cookies are used by us and our business partners to send you advertisements when using the Themer websites and apps and to target those adverts to you and your interests. In doing this our business partners may use the profiles they have developed of other apps and websites that you have previously visited. These cookies may also help us and our business partners regulate the adverts you receive and measure its effectiveness. If we let our business partners place the cookies for advertising we do not give your name, email address or phone number to those business partners.  
More information is available on the development of user-profiles, the targeting of advertising and how to stop the use of "targeting" cookies. Please see www.youronlinechoices.eu if you are located in Europe or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ if in the United States. Please note if you delete our cookies or disable future cookies you may not be able to fully use the Themer websites or apps. If you want to delete any cookies on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Your mobile operating system should also give you the option to manage your cookies and advertising preferences (this may be found in the "settings" function on your device).
  6. #### Sorry kids, over 13s only

We take our responsibilities to the online community very seriously. As such, if you are under the age of 13 we have to ask you not to use our apps or websites in any way. We don't knowingly collect data from anyone under the age of 13 and we do not direct any of our products or services at this age group. If we become aware that we have inadvertently captured any personal data about a person who is under 13 years of age, then we will take the appropriate steps to shut down the account of that person.
  7. #### How to access and correct your data (and a special note to Californian residents)

You can update your personal data through the Themer apps and you can ask us about what data we are holding by sending us an email. We will do our best to respond to your request (upon verification of your identity) within a reasonable period of time. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 also permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, a list of the third parties to whom we disclosed their personal data (if any) for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the categories of data disclosed to those third parties. To make any sort of access request, please email or write to us using the details above.
  8. #### Changes to this Themer Privacy Policy

Themer reserves the right to make changes to this Themer and MyColorScreen Privacy Policy, and will post any revisions on this page. 
  9. #### English version prevails

In the event that this Themer and MyColorScreen Privacy Policy is translated into other languages and there is a discrepancy between the two language versions, the English language version shall prevail to the extent that such discrepancy is the result of an error in translation. This policy is governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. 

#### Website

#### Registration and Password

Access to some of the Themer Website services require that you register with the Website. When you register on the Website, we will automatically create a public profile for you. Any profiles created will be available on the Website for others to view. You may at any time update your profile, or change your username and password.

Your registration details must be truthful and accurate and you agree to keep them up to date. Any email addresses or phone number you provide to us must be a valid email address and valid phone number.

Once you have a username and password, you will be responsible for all activities occurring under your username and for keeping your password secure. You agree to notify us immediately if you are aware of any loss, theft, or unauthorized use of your user name or password.

We may prompt you to change your username or deactivate your account, temporarily or permanently, if we believe that in using the name you are attempting to impersonate another person, or that it infringes or may infringe a trademark, breaches any law, is vulgar, offensive or is otherwise inappropriate.

#### Personal Use

These Services are available for your personal use only and you may not use the Services for any commercial purpose. We may restrict or terminate your access to the Services, at any time, without notice, if you are in breach of the Terms.

#### Unsolicited Ideas and Feedback

We welcome your feedback on what we are currently doing (both positive and negative). If you want to send us your feedback, we ask that you use our contact form. Any feedback you provide to us can be used by us on an unrestricted basis and treated by us as non-confidential.

Please note the following caution. Please do not tell us anything that contains new or original ideas, in respect of which you might want, now or in future, to claim any form of proprietary rights. Please do not submit any such ideas, original creative material, suggestions or other work in any form to us. We ask this because we want to avoid potential misunderstandings or disputes if our products might seem similar to ideas submitted to us.

If, despite our request that you not send us your ideas, you still send them to us, then regardless of what you say to us, you agree that: (i) your submissions and their contents will automatically become our property, without any compensation to you, you will not assert against us any rights or ownership and you will not claim any reward (financial or otherwise) in respect of any such submissions; (ii) we may use or redistribute the submissions and their contents for any purpose and in any way; (iii) there is no obligation for us to review any material that you submit to us; and (iv) there is no obligation to keep any such material confidential.
